Guide to the Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015.]
Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015]
- Series IV. Videotapes
  - Subseries IVa. Videotapes transferred from Distributed Learning Services
    - Streambank Fencing/Cows, Wet Fields, PSU, John Dickison, OFC 220, V-4345; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 61)
    - Pyramid Mall, B-Roll, Tape 1, OFC-221, February 6, 1995; V-4346; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Pulaski, Small Business Program, 3A-B, 2 Tapes, OFC-251-252, March 1, 1995; V-4347 - V-4348; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Food Insecurity, 1A-1B, 2B, 3A-3B, 5 Tapes, OFC-253-257, March 8-22, 1995; V-4349 - V-4353; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Onsite Sewage, Rick Ewald, Tape 1A-1B, 2B, 3 Tapes, OFC-258-261, August 24, 1994; V-4354 - V-4357; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Septic Pick-ups, Part 2, OFC-262, December 22, 1994; V-4358; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - OSST B-Roll, OFC-263, V-4359; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Women In Leadership Tapes 1A-5B, December 2, 1994; V-4360 - V-4369; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Princeton Press Box 1 (Box says Tape #1, cassette says Tape #3), SB-2 T-1, September 17, 1988; V-4370; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Princeton Press Box 1, SB-2 T-2, V-4371; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Princeton Field 1-2, SB-2 T-3 - T-4, September 17, 1988; V-4372 - V-4373; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Harvard Press Box 1-3, SB-2 T-5 - T-7, October 8, 1988; V-4374 - V-4376; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Harvard Field 1-2, SB-2 T-8 - T-9, October 8, 1988; V-4377 - V-4378; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Harvard Pregame, SB-2 T-10, October 8, 1988; V-4379; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Spring Campus, CF 08, May 10, 1991; V-4380; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Interactive Multimedia Group Tape 1, DOF 02, September 13, 1991; V-4381; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Cornell University Convocation May '92 - Geraldine Ferraro, V-4382; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Plantations - Deans Garden, walkway near Flat Rock, #11, September 26, 1995; V-4383; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Plantations - Beebe Lake Stairs Trail, #14, October 17, 1995; V-4384; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - B-Roll - AD White Garden, June 28, 2000; V-4385; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - B-Roll - Plantations, new employee orientation, July 18, 2000; V-4386; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - B-Roll, HR - Collegetown Campus, September 13, 2000; V-4387; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - B-Roll, HR, September 26, 2000; V-4388; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - B-Roll, HR - Bike Shot, September 13, 2002; V-4389; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - China Nutrition: London Conference 3A-2A, OFC292 - OFC294, January 21, 1994; V-4390 - V-4392; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 62)
    - Financial Management for Older Youth Segments, Mixed Master, PD07, October 26, 1992; V-4393; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Cooperation Works: Achieving Community Benefits Through Alliances Networks and Cooperatives, Tape 1, SAT105, April 5, 1995; V-4394; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - CaRDI: Newly Elected Officials, program 1, Tape 2, SAT138, December 11, 1995; V-4395; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Bio-Diversity Master for Biodiversity Farm & Forests, UN22, November 30, 1994; V-4396; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - BCA: Women Active, Pt. 1, Edit Master, August 6, 1996; V-4397; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - BCA Pt. 2, Edit Master, August 6, 1996; V-4398; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Focus Group, Tapes #1-2, Home #6-#7, September 18, 1996; V-4399 - V-4400; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Knight Labs for RBS short course, V-4401; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Moving Backgrounds, *from Fox Network feeds, November 1996; V-4402; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Nano Knight Labs, Irv Chapman, Tape #1, May 25, 1988; V-4403; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Nano Knight Labs, Irv Chapman, Tape #2, May 25, 1988; V-4404; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Not in my school, not in my community, Pt. 1 of 2, V-4405; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Plantations - - Gross, Tape #2, June 12, 1990; V-4406; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - George Will, June 8, 1990; V-4407; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Cornell @ Colgate, Tape 1, January 22, 1991; V-4408 - V-4410; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - Harvard vs. Cornell B-Ball, Tapes 1-2, February 23, 1990; V-4411 - V-4412; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - CU vs RPI Hockey, Periods 1-3, February 24, 1990; V-4413 - V-4415; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 63)
    - A Day of Remembrance: Cornell Honors the Victims of the September 11th Terrorist Attacks on America, September 14, 2001; V-4416; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Gould Colman, "History of Cornell", October 22, 1992; V-4417; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - History of TV, Mike T., Interactive video, PD05, May 11, 1991; V-4418; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - President Lee at Cornell: Speech, SAT118, June 9, 1995; V-4419 - V-4420; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - L.R. Severinghaus and Henry R. Luce Return to China-1932, Tapes 1-2, PC44 - PC45, V-4421 - V-4422; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Around the World with BA Garside, Film TX, VI, PC46, V-4423; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - FB 92 Teacher Features (9/2); Franklin Robinson(9/10); Don Randal (9/18); Mary Sansalone (9/28), PD67, 1992; V-4424; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Karel Husa on TV Nova, PD99, December 16, 1993; V-4425; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Beans, Tape #2, July 28, 1987; V-4426; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Redox Titration, Thin Chromatography, (Tape A), Cornell University, V-4427; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Fractional Distillation-205, (Tape A), Cornell University, V-4428; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Intro to the Lab, Glassworking Techniques, (Tape B), Cornell University, V-4429; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Visible Absorption Spectrometry, Separatory Funnels, (Tape B), Cornell University, V-4430; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Atomic Absorption Spectrophotometry, Column Chromotography, (Tape C), Cornell University, V-4431; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Volumetric Flask II 300, Pipetting 300 (Blue Bulb), (Tape D), Cornell University, V-4432; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Vacuum Filtration in Gravimetric Analysis, (Tape D), Cornell University, V-4433; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Athletics, C.U. Football, '80, 1980; V-4434; ¾" U-matic (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - The Arts: A Conversation with John Cage, V-4435; ¾" U-matic (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Shoals Marine Lab, Master and Raw Footage, October 8, 1990; V-4436; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - US Attorney General Janet Reno, Lecture at Barton Hall, Cornell University, AD46, October 20, 1994; V-4437; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - New Prez. News Conference, Tapes 1-3, H. Rawlings, AD47 - AD49, December 10, 1994; V-4438 - V-4440; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - NYS Lottery, "Cornell Winner: Al and Judy Herrala" Press Conference, AD50, November 4, 1994; V-4441; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Dean Call's Retirement, Tapes 1-3, AD71 - AD73, May 1, 1995; V-4442 - V-4444; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Dean Call's Retirement, Podium cam, Tapes 1-4, AD74 - AD77, May 1, 1995; V-4445 - V-4448; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - (A.D. White) "5 Presidents" Rawlings Inaug., AD91, October 12, 1995; V-4449; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Forest Decline, Computer Model, Ron Beloin, DOF39, December 8, 1988; V-4450; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Cornell Sports Network, Dr. David Feldshuh, Center for Theatre Arts, October 9, 1991; V-4451; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 64)
    - Cornell News Service, "Mars Sundial," Press Conference with Bill Nye, April 21, 1999; V-4452; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Near Mathilde and Eros, Fly By's, master, May 26, 1999; V-4453; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Today Show w/ Alfred Kahn, October 24, 1988; V-4454; ½" VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Acquired Documentaries, Blue Sky Below My Feet #1: Gravity & Forces, V-4455; U-matic (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Dalai Lama, Interview in Studio, CNN News, INT 13, March 27, 1991; V-4456; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Alfred Kahn, Interview for CNN, INT 74, May 27, 1993; V-4457; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Cornell Graduation, Tape 1-2, 2 Tapes, SAT 11-12, May 24, 1992; V-4458 - V-4459; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - First Lay Hillary Clinton at Barton Hall, SAT 23, November 4, 1993; V-4460; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Cornell Commencement 1991, 3 Tapes, SAT 65-67, May 1991; V-4461 - V-4463; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Thomas Eisner: National Medal of Sciences and Technoly, SAT 81, December 19, 1994; V-4464; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Live Interview with Meredith Small for Fox Network in Detroit, MI, SAT 104, March 27, 1995; V-4465; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Cornell Commencement 1995, Tape 3, ETV Recording, SAT 113, May 28, 1995; V-4466; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Renee Gusa, Steve Ceci/HDFS, December 10, 1988, November 16, 1993; V-4467; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Yale, ESPN, 4 Tapes, SB-4 T-1 - T-4, November 5, 1988; V-4468 - V-4471; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Yale, Homecoming Breakfast, 2 Tapes, SB-4 T-5 - T-6, November 5, 1988; V-4472 - V-4473; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Yale, Coaches Press Box, SB-4 T-7, November 5, 1988; V-4474; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Yale, Field Camera - 1, SB-4 T-8, November 5, 1988; V-4475; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Press Conference, Foutes New Football Coach, SB-9 T-1 - T-2, April 26, 1989; V-4476 - V-4477; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Golf Outing #1-2, SB-9 T-3 - T-4, August 10, 1989; V-4478 - V-4479; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Spring F.B. day #1, SB-9 T-5, May 7, 1989; V-4480 - V-4482; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 65)
    - Spring F.B. day #1, SB-9 T-6 - T-7, May 7, 1989; V-4481 - V-4482; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Player Interviews #1, SB-9 T-8 - T-9, November 28, 1989; V-4483 - V-4484; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Player Interviews #1, SB-9 T-10, November 28, 1989; V-4485; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Columbia @ Cornell basketball, Reels 1-2, January 20, 1990; V-4486 - V-4487; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - CU vs. Colgate football, Reels 1-3, September 22, 1990; V-4488 - V-4490; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Cornell vs. Clarkson hockey, Tapes 1-3, February 2, 1991; V-4491 - V-4493; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - CU Hockey vs. Harvard, Period 3, December 3, 1989; V-4494; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Hockey Vermont, 2nd period, February 23, 1991; V-4495; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Cornell @ Brown, Tapes #1-2, November 2, 1991; V-4496 - V-4497; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Cornell @ Dartmouth, Tapes #1-2, October 26, 1991; V-4498 - V-4499; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - CU @ Penn Football, Reels 1-2, November 23, 1991; V-4500 - V-4501; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Cornell vs. Princeton Football, Tape #2, September 21, 1991; V-4502; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Yale @ Cornell, Tapes #1-2, November 9, 1991; V-4503 - V-4504; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 66)
    - Coop. Works, "Powerful Concept" (intro seg.) No music, AIR85, V-4505; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Oswego Assoc. Small Business Program, AIR88, March 10, 1995; V-4506; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Synernet Cooperative (mixed), AIR90, April 4, 1995; V-4507; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Cattaragaus County Partnership meeting 5A, OFC209, March 31, 1994; V-4508; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Chief Executives Network, UN27, March 29, 1995; V-4509; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Windmill Farm and Craft Market, edited master (unmixed), UN28, March 28, 1995; V-4510; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Beans #2, August 7, 1987; V-4511; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Rushing Waters, May 28, 1996; V-4512; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - New Berlin- Flowers Youth and Elderly, Tape #1, March 17, 1997; V-4513; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Not in Our Schools 2, B-roll- Halls, lockers, and stuff, May 27, 1999; V-4514; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - C.S.N. Tracks- 1. Ferguson and 2. Ratughny, January 15, 1991; V-4515; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Harvey Gant Interview, Tape #2, January 29, 1991; V-4516; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Student Bistro, February 5, 1991; V-4517; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - SPIF C.C.R. Tape #1, February 12, 1991; V-4518; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - John Condry, TV viewing, February 18, 1991; V-4519; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Sciencecenter Tape #2, February 23, 1991; V-4520; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Polo- Coach/Captains interviews, March 4, 1991; V-4521; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Condry, TV, B-Roll, March 4, 1991; V-4522; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - CCR open, new, March 8, 1991; V-4523; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Dalai Lama, weather calendar, V-4524; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - TQM Interviews, May 24, 1994; V-4525; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - TQM in Local Gov't, Aud. Cam., 1A-2B, May 24, 1994; V-4526 - V-4529; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - TQM Pod, Tapes 1A-3A, May 24, 1994; V-4530 - V-4534; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Morrison, Altra Sonic Beef 4, AG 20, May 2, 1988; V-4536; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - T&R, Buf Poague, AG 22, April 20, 1988; V-4537; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Empire Farm Days" IPM Sprayer Demo, DOS 06, July 6, 1992; V-4535; BETA 10 (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Roth #2, DOS 10, March 13, 1990; V-4538; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Forest Decline, Reel 4, SC 07, November 23, 1987; V-4539; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Forest Decline, Lab-Work, #5, SC 08, November 23, 1987; V-4540; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Forest Delcine, SC 09, June 1988; V-4541; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Forest Decline Research, Acid Rain, SC 10, July 12, 1988; V-4542; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - BTI, Seed Storage, SC 14, July 16, 1990; V-4543; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Forest Decline, Rain Collectors, Chamber, Tape 12, SC 15, September 14, 1988; V-4544; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Dairy Farm, Lab #2, Tape 3, SC 23, March 8, 1988; V-4545; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Cornell Sports Network, Tim Lee, B-Roll, Matt McLean Intervew, B-Roll, SC 24, October 5, 1992; V-4546; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - Matt McLean Scholar, Athlete, Bio Lab, SC 25, October 6, 1992; V-4547; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - NAIC, 1A, SC 32, April 13, 1995; V-4548; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - C-Roll, Ryan, September 28; V-4549; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 67)
    - B-Roll, September 28, 1994; V-4550; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Stock Footage "Campus", V-4551; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Training Development Seminar, Judith Ross-Berstren, Tape 3, October 8, 1999; V-4552; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Purple Loosestrife Interviews, Tapes 1-3, 3 Tapes, October 4, 1995; V-4553 - V-4555; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Rearing Techniques for Bio Control Agents Fish Lab, Tapes A2-A7, 6 Tapes, June 2 - September 15, 1997; V-4556 - V-4561; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - DEA/P. Eshelman, "Alzheimer's" Project (MVR Living Space), 4 Tapes, December 12, 1995; V-4562 - V-4565; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - PEP-Edited Version, "Most" of Tapes #2, V-4566 - V-4567; BETA 10 (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - "Inauguration of Hunter Rawlings, Part 1 68 V-4569 - V-4579 Beta 6.1x3.8""", V-4568; BETA 10 (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Cornell Tradition, IHT 41, June 23, 1987; V-4580; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Apples Tape 7, OFC 101, October 6, 1988; V-4581; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Breast Cancer Risk (Bcerf), grocery shopping @ Wegman's, basketball practice, 81, January 9, 1997; V-4582; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Bcerf2, Elizabeth Hess Interview, Tape 2B, 384, August 1, 1997; V-4583; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Bcerf2, Intergenerational Family, Tape 4A, 387, August 26, 1997; V-4584; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Cornell Orchards, October 17, 1990; V-4585; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - CSN B-Roll, October 16, 1990; V-4586; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - CSN Audio Cuts, November 14, 1990; V-4587; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Double Income Families, June 18, 1990; V-4588; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Food Security, September 6, 1996; V-4589; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 68)
    - Just Say No; Call Collect, V-4590; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Kids as Consumers (Wegmans) Tapes 2-3, February 22, 1996; V-4591 - V-4592; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - P-HCPC Tape 2B, January 29, 1998; V-4593; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - P-HCPC - 2B Exam, March 4, 1998; V-4594; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Wood Carver, Tapes 1-2, June 18, 1990; V-4595 - V-4596; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - 4-H, V-4597; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - 4-H, Brochere, Take #2, V-4598; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Albany, Newly Elected Officials, John Haspen, John Kelly, Ann Tucker Rose, State Comptroller, Tape 1, December 5, 1995; V-4599; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Poss Banking Shot, RP-102,103,104, 3 Tapes, V-4600 - V-4602; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Banking, Tape 2, Cam 2, Commons and Trip Theatre, RP-105, August 18, 1986; V-4603; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Banking, Greater Ithaca, #1, RP106, August 20, 1986; V-4604; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Banking, Battery Park, Cam 2, Tape 1, RP107, September 3, 1986; V-4605; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Banking, Battery Park, Cam 1, Tape 3, RP108, September 3, 1986; V-4606; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Hatch #33, Liming, #2, Cam 2, RP109, September 16, 1986; V-4607; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Banking, Battery Park, Cam 2, Tape 2, RP110, September 3, 1986; V-4608; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Manny's Narration, RP111, V-4609; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Cardi, Part 2, December 9-12, 1995; V-4610; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - CSN, Students, Music, B-Roll, September 7, 1994; V-4611; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Financial Freeway, DM-Edit, December 19, 1995; V-4612; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Mike Kelly, Segments, December 12, 1995; V-4613; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Onsite Wastewater, Auburn Conferene, #1-#10, 10 Tapes, 1A-5B, May 1994; V-4614 - V4623; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Onsite Wastewater, Auburn Conference, #12-#13, 6B-7A, February 22, 1994; V-4624 - V-4625; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - RTS/Deck Test for Hits, Oxide Tape, February 10, 1998; V-4626; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Southside Playground Update, February 27, 1991; V-4627; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Trustee Dinner, 2 Tapes, 1A-B, October 13, 1995; V-4628 - V-4629; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Camera Test Bars, Thomson, 350, Chip and Bar Chart, Studio, V-4630; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Panasonic Test Tape, F-565, V-4631; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - B-Roll CAD Lab Tape 3, OFC 222, V-4632; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - B-Roll CAD Lab Tape 4, OFC 223, V-4633; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Adrian Jules B-Roll CAD, OFC 224, V-4634; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Food Pantry Tape 2, OFC 225, V-4635; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - C.E.N. Albany Tape 1A, OFC 226, February 23, 1995; V-4636; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 69)
    - Windmill B-Roll Tape 2A, OFC 227, October 1, 1994; V-4637; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Windmill B-Roll Tape 1B, OFC 228, October 1, 1994; V-4638; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Cooperation Works Windmill Tape 1A, OFC 229, October 1, 1994; V-4639; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - C.E.N. Albany Passonno Paints Tape 2A, OFC 230, February 23, 1995; V-4640; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - CEN - Kintz Plastics Cobleskill, OFC 231, February 24, 1995; V-4641; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Synernet - Mercy Hospital Portland ME Tape 3A, OFC 232, February 22, 1995; V-4642; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Synernet York Hospital Tape 2B, OFC 233, February 21, 1995; V-4643; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Synernet Work Comp. Linda Riddell Interview Tape 2A, OFC 234, February 21, 1995; V-4644; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - CEN Albany 1A Diamond in Products, OFC 235, February 23, 1995; V-4645; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Thunderstorm, OFC 236, August 28, 1994; V-4646; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - OSTS Onsite Sewage Open Footage 1 of 2, OFC 237, V-4647; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - OSTS Onsite Sewage Open Footage 2 of 2, OFC 238, V-4648; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Gypsy Moth News Reports from Nassau County, OFC 239, October 1994; V-4649; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Terri Nipp B-Roll Tape 2, OFC 240, V-4650; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Open House NYC Ext. Office, Tapes 1-2, OFC 241 - OFC 242, June 23, 1994; V-4651 - V-4652; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Allegany Association Youth Programs Tapes 1A - 2B, OFC 243 - OFC 246, December 15, 1994; V-4653 - V-4656; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Pulaski - Small Business Program Tapes 1A-1B, OFC 247 - OFC 248, February 28, 1995; V-4657 - V-4658; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Random Stuff, OFC 266, V-4659; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Home Exterior, OFC 267, May 26, 1994; V-4660; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Cardi Spencer V-E Breakfast Club Tape 1B, OFC 268, May 4, 1995; V-4661; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Geneva Economic Development Program Tapes 1A-1B, OFC 269 - OFC 270, May 15, 1995; V-4662 - V-4663; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Bunker Silos 1A: Twin Burch Farms I & II, OFC 271 - OFC 272, June 2, 1993; V-4664 - V-4665; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Bunker Silos 2A: Fessenden Farm, OFC 273, June 3, 1993; V-4666; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Bunker Silos 10A: Raymond Farm, OFC 274, September 30, 1993; V-4667; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Bunker Silos Tape 10B, OFC 275, September 30, 1993; V-4668; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Bunker Silos Tape 11A, OFC 276, October 1, 1993; V-4669; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)
    - Bunker Silos Tape 7A, OFC 277, March 29, 1994; V-4670; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 70)